All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
After a change of plans, Horty threatens to crush the entire island under the weight of a massive ship.
We've just been informed it's lost power.
As a result, it's begun falling again and it's hurtling towards the island!
Goodness, no!
He spoke earlier and...
It's clear now, Horty is...
He's not a fishman.
He's a monster brought to life by our hatred.
The New Fishman Pirates, they're nothing but remnants of a grudge from ages past.
Answer me, dammit!
What did humans do to you that was so unforgivable?
Why?
What in this world could inspire such cruelty?
Not one damn thing.
The simple truth, we were chosen by heaven to punish the humans.
That is our purpose.
And we have the power to do so.
All of their fury, their hatred, it doesn't come from experience or logic or fact.
They have no substance.
Just empty cruelty.
Back to Zero, Ernest wishes for Luffy.
Their hatred, it doesn't come from experience or logic or fact.
They have no substance.
Just empty cruelty.
So now what?
I get what he's saying, but how are they going to stop them?
Hey, what are you standing around for?
We've got to get off the island right now!
I can see the shadow of the Nua already!
It's right over our heads!
Keep your eyes peeled.
It's almost in range.
I know that.
Our time is running out.
How much inflation do we have to work with right now?
About 87%.
Here it comes.
Let's get ready!
Hurry with me, Hoshi!
What's happening?
He looks even more frightening than before!
Humans are worthless.
Evil creatures.
Never forget that, Hordi.
They're scum.
Barely fit to serve us.
This is it!
We're done for!
Ever since the Great Pirate Era started, we've been losing more and more of our people every day!
The humans take the mermaids to Sabo-Odi and sell them off.
Some of them went missing this morning!
I'm telling you, it's just a matter of time before Fishman Island falls!
Filthy humans?
We've got to kill them before they kill us!
Yeah, we can't leave a single one alive!
Damn.
Humans are the worst.
Yeah, humans suck!
If you got stronger, I see he!
Amazing!
Fishman Island has a new hero!
Listen up!
This man sacrificed his life to blow up the human shop and set the slaves free!
Pay your respects!
Hero, huh?
That guy's awesome!
Sure is!
Yeah, that's what I want to be!
Count me in!
Tch!
Have you heard the news?
Orlong sank another human pirate ship!
Now, I'll tell you about those wretched worms called humans.
Ages ago, when they realized that we the fishmen were the superior race, they became jealous
and froide.
became jealous and afraid, and then they began to persecute our people.
The human race plagued the entire world like the vermin they are.
They used their numbers to gain dominance over our people.
Then all of us fishmen were driven down here to the sea floor.
Listen to me, and don't forget this.
The humans know that they will one day face retribution for the wrongs they have inflicted
upon us.
We'll settle the score and make them suffer.
Remember the plight of our people.
Let yourself feel the bitterness of those who've passed on, and make their resentment your own.
Hold fast to your anger.
There's this really nice human name Rayleigh I made friends with on the surface.
And he's not mean like the rest are, he doesn't even look that disgusted when he sees me.
Wait Hordy, where are you going?
I don't like your stupid stories Hachi, they make me sick.
Humans fear the fishmen, you must keep the bitterness of the dead alive Hordy.
Remember our past, the very existence of humanity is pure evil.
You must hate them, hate them, hate them, hate them!
This is terrible, Tiger's been slain by humans!
The hero of the fishmen is dead!
It seems Tiger was not the hero we needed.
The hero of the people, what do you want?
Is it true you gave your blood to humans?
So what if I did?
He was dying, I had to help!
This whole country's mad, right down to the royal family.
The queen's looking to make nice with the humans.
How stupid can you be?
Jinbei too, heard he joined the seven warlords recently.
The hour long pirates are the only ones who ain't pride these days.
For what?
We need a new kind of hero.
Huh?
Gah?
Someone who has no fear.
Someone who can set this country straight.
Queen Odohime has been shot!
You see?
The humans are evil.
They would even stoop so low as to kill the queen, and after she's been so kind to them.
If the royal family is too meek to hold the humans accountable, then I can't be loyal to this kingdom anymore!
I don't want to be ruled by a bunch of cowards!
The heavens have repaid that spineless Odohime for bowing.
Anyone who wants to forgive humans deserves a big dose into the head!
I hope you're ready, boys.
It's our turn now.
We've been chosen by the heavens, granted this unstoppable power.
Is that what I think it is?
Those are legendary here!
How did you get your hands on this?
You can duplicate these, can't you?
I'll try.
The people of the Fishman District must come together.
Our proud crusade is about to begin.
No mercy!
We'll kill as many humans as we can until the day we die.
This is our destiny.
We've been chosen by heaven to bring about the revolution.
The day of reckoning is coming.
This is the end of the road for all of you.
We've been biding our time for long enough.
Now we'll take our revenge at last.
We could have stopped all this.
I see now.
The Royal Family turned their eyes away from the Fishman District.
In our negligence, we allowed it to become a breeding ground for violence and hatred.
We could have stopped all this.
I see now. The Royal Family turned their eyes away from the Fishman District.
In our negligence, we allowed it to become a breeding ground for violence and hatred.
We pretended not to see the resentment that built up as a result of their isolation.
Even as it descended into lawlessness, we lived in willful ignorance.
Not so fast! You going somewhere?
We have to run! The No-
I don't think so!
I thought collecting those signatures would help, but I wasn't addressing the true issue.
Please forgive me, Mother. I'm so sorry.
I know it's difficult, but you can't pollute the children's minds with your anger towards humans.
Your resentment, do not make it theirs!
But it was too late! Despite all her pleading, the things she feared had already been set in motion!
Oh, Fukuboshi!
The real enemy was the resentment brewing inside our hearts.
I felt it too, that hatred.
But refusing to admit that, I looked outward when I should have looked inward.
My mother's true killer was the grudge that festered among our people while we turned a blind eye!
The real enemy was the resentment brewing inside our hearts.
I felt it too, that hatred.
But refusing to admit that, I looked outward when I should have looked inward.
My mother's true killer was the grudge that festered among our people while we turned a blind eye!
And I believe she knew it in that very moment!
My dear children, it doesn't matter who hurt me. Don't become angry. Please, not on my behalf.
Don't submit to resentment. Don't let hatred get the better of you, in my name or any other.
I listened to my mother's words, but part of me wasn't able to let go of my anger.
I couldn't help but hate humans for killing her!
Me neither!
A person's pain dies with them.
I don't know who hurt me.
I don't know who hurt me. Don't become angry. Please, not on my behalf.
Don't submit to resentment. Don't let hatred get the better of you, in my name or any other.
I listened to my mother's words, but part of me wasn't able to let go of my anger.
I couldn't help but hate humans for killing her!
Me neither!
A person's pain dies with them. A grudge is created by the living, and only the living make it grow stronger.
Because of my prejudice, I overlooked what was happening in the Fishman district.
And by the time I came to my senses, it was already spiraling out of control!
If we don't do something soon, the people of Fishman Island will be done in by their own hatred, a foe more deadly than any human!
No!
This'll be tough, man. It's not like the island's bubble. It might shoot right past the Noah.
It needs to get close enough to surround it. No more, no less.
Straw Hat! Please!
Erase our past! Set us back to zero! Eradicate the shadows cast by our grudge so that we may see the light!
Okay. Get ready to fire!
I'm on it!
Here we go!
All we can do is start over! We must!
Would you give it a rest already? The rage of our people will never die!
Brother Hoshi!
Just let me do this my way! Trust me!
Hey, wait a second! Those guys fighting Horty's crew in the plaza! Aren't they?
Yeah! You're right! They're the Straw Hat Pirates!
And Boss Jinbei too!
What?
That's Luffy's voice!
You're right!
Room To tengan No quicker you should.
To get into disaster being
We did it! It's in the bubble!
Our minds were made up as soon as we got to the plaza. With Jinbei's help, we were gonna save this island! Leave it to me and my crew!
That's what friends are for, right?
We should never have suspected him, human or not!
What's the hold-up?
We should go!
Hurry up! Run!
I think I'm gonna stay here.
What?
Me too!
Yeah, same here!
I am not running away!
Me neither!
Luffy! There's air on the Noah!
Yeah!
That may be, but I'm going to catch you along before you get there!
What should we do, Luffy?
You'll be okay. Just follow my lead and I promise I won't let Hordy hurt you!
Yes, right!
Feeling brave?
Careful, Luffy!
That machine's no match for the spirit of the squid!
Spirit!
That's not spirit!
That's just spit!
Ink!
Fortunately, I can copy myself with squidding!
The spirit of the squid is unstuffed!
Fireball!
No, I don't want to be dried squid!
Wow!
I didn't know your robot could shoot fireballs!
How many cool attacks can this baby do?
Wait! That came out of you?
You really shouldn't have let your guard down, little guy!
Yeah, like I would!
Wait for it!
Three shot!
Heavy gun!
Who uses their bare hand to stop a hammer?
On second thought, I probably could have found a less painful way to do that!
Hey, Chopper!
I thought that one was supposed to be your normal looking form!
Sure you're okay looking so freaky?
Haha!
I don't care anymore!
I wanted to look human before, because I didn't have any friends!
But now, I want to be a monster so I can help Luffy!
Gotcha!
I'll slice that smile right off your face!
Bring me the real strongest swordsman on Fishman Island!
There's no way it's you!
I didn't even break a sweat!
Got you now!
Sorry!
But your time is up!
Did you hear a word that I said?
I'm gonna save them all!
From you and anything you've got!
The battle against the new Fishman Pirates races towards its climax in Concord Plaza.
Meanwhile, in the open sea, Hordy mercilessly pummels Luffy in a fit of rage.
However, Luffy is determined to keep his promise to Fukuboshi and unleashes his most deadly attack
in hopes of finishing the battle before it's too late.
On the next One Piece, Luffy's all-out attack, Red Hawk Blast!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!